Erwin Panofsky
Archives of American Art, Smithsonian Institution
- Correspondence, 1921-1978, undated, Series 1:; (Boxes 1-16; 16 linear ft. Reels 2108-2128)
  - Colleagues, Scholars, Students and Other Individuals, 1921-1978, undated, 1.1:
    - Walker, 1948-1966 (Box 13, Reel 2124)
      Walker, Robert
    - Wallace, Richard W., 1959-1968 (Box 13, Reel 2124)
    - Warburg - Warren, 1940-1964 (Box 13, Reel 2124)
      Warburg, Anita
      Warburg, Edward M. M.
      Warburg, Max
      Ward, Clarence
      Warren, Edith
    - Wasson, R. Gordon, 1950-1957 (Box 13, Reel 2124)
    - Waterhouse - Weinmann, 1946-1965 (Box 13, Reel 2124)
      Waterhouse, Ellis K.
      Webster-Bulatkin, Eleanor
      Weinberg, Bernard
      Weinberger, Martin
      Weinmann, Françoise
    - Weisinger, Herbert, 1946-1965 (Box 13, Reel 2124)
    - Weitenkampt - Weitzmann, 1951-1965 (Box 13, Reel 2124)
      Weitenkampf, Frank
      Weitzmann, Kurt
    - Weixlgärtner, Arpad and Josephine, 1950-1963, undated (Box 13, Reel 2124)
    - Welliver - Wengroth, 1956-1958, undated (Box 13, Reel 2124)
      Welliver, Mrs. Charles B.
      Welliver, Warman
      Welsh, Sue
      Wengroth, Stow
    - Wentzel, Hans, 1950-1975 (Box 13, Reel 2124)
    - Wershba - Wethey, 1941-1961 (Box 13, Reel 2124)
      Wershba, Joe
      Wescher, Paul
      Wethey, Harold E.
    - White, John, 1950-1955 (Box 13, Reel 2124)
    - White, Lynn, 1938-1967 (Box 13, Reel 2124)
    - Wildenstein, Georges, 1945-1961 (Box 13, Reel 2124)
    - Will - Winkler, 1938-1967, undated (Box 13, Reel 2124)
      Will, Frederic
      Willert, Paul
      Wilhelm, Pia
      Wilson, Larry
      Wind, Edgar
      Winkler, Friederich
    - Winternitz, Emmanuel, 1953-1966 (Box 13, Reel 2124)
    - Witte, Wilhelm, 1961 (Box 13, Reel 2124)
    - Wittkower, Rudolph, 1936-1971 (Box 13, Reel 2124)
    - Woodford, Susan, 1966 (Box 13, Reel 2124)
    - Wolff, Kurt, 1942-1960 (Box 13, Reel 2124)
    - Woodward, Llewellyn, 1957-1962 (Box 13, Reel 2124)
    - Wormald, Francis, 1937-1967 (Box 13, Reel 2124)
    - Wrightsman - Wuttke, 1953-1972, undated (Box 13, Reel 2124)
      Wrightsman, C. B.
      Wuttke, Dieter
    - Xydis - Zeitler, 1945-1967 (Box 13, Reel 2124)
      Xydis, Stephen
      Yates, Frances
      Young, Mrs. T. R.
      Zados-Jitta, A. N.
      Zaffrani, Gian Franca
      Zannetti, Mario
      Zarnecki, George
      Zebal, Kinta A.
      Ziegermann, Erich
      Ziegermann, Peter
      Zeitlin, J.
      Zeitler, Rudolf
    - Zerner - Zupnick, 1937-1969 (Box 13, Reel 2124)
      Zerner, Henri
      Zigrosser, Carl
      Zilsel, E.
      Zimmerman, Mary H.
      Zucker, Paul
      Zupnick, I. L.
  - Art Dealers, 1932-1967, 1.2:
    - England (Colnaghi - Sotheby), 1950-1965 (Box 13, Reel 2124)
    - France (Rheims and Baudoin), 1932 (Box 13, Reel 2124)
    - Holland/Netherlands (Kunsthandel P. de Boer), 1958-1962 (Box 13, Reel 2124)
    - United States (Box 13, Reel 2124-2125)
      - Mortimer Brandt Gallery, 1950-1966 (Box 13, Reel 2124-2125)
      - Buchholz Gallery; Paul Drey Gallery, 1946-1966 (Box 13, Reel 2124-2125)
      - Duveen Brothers; M. Knoedler; F. B. May Fine Arts, 1936-1966 (Box 13, Reel 2124-2125)
      - Parke-Bernet Galleries; Rosenberg and Stiebel, 1948-1963 (Box 13, Reel 2124-2125)
      - Schaeffer Galleries, Inc., 1936-1967 (Box 13, Reel 2124-2125)
      - E. and A. Silberman Galleries, 1943-1949 (Box 13, Reel 2124-2125)
  - Galleries and Museums, 1925-1968, 1.3:
    - Australia - National Gallery of Victoria, 1959-1968 (Box 13, Reel 2125)
    - Austria (Kunsthistorisches Museum), 1965 (Box 13, Reel 2125)
    - Belgium (Box 13, Reel 2125)
      - Damme (Museum van Maerlant), 1959 (Box 13, Reel 2125)
      - Antwerp (Musée Mayer van der Bergh; Musée Royale des Beaux Arts), 1949-1950 (Box 13, Reel 2125)
      - Ghent (Musée des Beaux-Arts), 1952-1957 (Box 13, Reel 2125)
    - Canada (Box 13, Reel 2125)
      - Kingston (Agnes Etherington Art Centre, Queen's University), 1968 (Box 13, Reel 2125)
      - Ottawa (National Gallery of Canada), 1955-1956 (Box 13, Reel 2125)
      - Winnepeg (Winnipeg Art Gallery), 1966 (Box 13, Reel 2125)
    - England (Box 13, Reel 2125)
      - Birmingham (Barber Institute of Fine Arts), 1954 (Box 13, Reel 2125)
      - Cambridge (Fitzwilliam Museum), 1948-1961 (Box 13, Reel 2125)
      - Leeds (City Art Gallery and Temple Newsam House), 1954 (Box 13, Reel 2125)
      - London (British Museum; National Gallery; Sir John Soane's Museum), 1925-1961 (Box 13, Reel 2125)
      - Manchester (Manchester City Art Gallery), 1954 (Box 13, Reel 2125)
      - Oxford (Ashmolean Museum), 1953-1955 (Box 13, Reel 2125)
      - York (City of York Art Gallery), 1955-1961 (Box 13, Reel 2125)
    - France (Box 13, Reel 2125)
      - Aix en Provence (Musée Granet), 1949 (Box 13, Reel 2125)
      - Fontainebleau (Musée de Fontainebleau), 1956-1958 (Box 13, Reel 2125)
      - Lyon (Lyon Musée des Beaux-Arts), 1954-1955 (Box 13, Reel 2125)
      - Nancy (Musée des Beaux-Arts), 1951 (Box 13, Reel 2125)
      - Orléans (Musée des Beaux-Arts), 1958 (Box 13, Reel 2125)
      - Paris (Musée de Louvre), 1951-1955 (Box 13, Reel 2125)
    - Germany (Box 13, Reel 2125)
      - Berlin (Staatlichen Museen zu Berlin), 1955 (Box 13, Reel 2125)
      - Dortmund (Museum für Kunst und Kulturgeschichte Dortmund), 1959 (Box 13, Reel 2125)
      - Hamburg (Museum für Kunst und Gewrbe), 1951-1957 (Box 13, Reel 2125)
    - Holland/Netherlands (Box 13, Reel 2125)
      - Amsterdam (Rijksmuseum), 1951-1965 (Box 13, Reel 2125)
      - The Hague (Box 13, Reel 2125)
        - Mauritshuis, 1947-1965 (Box 13, Reel 2125)
        - Meermanno-Westreenianum, 1951 (Box 13, Reel 2125)
        - ???sHertogenbosch, 1966-1967 (Box 13, Reel 2125)
      - Utrecht (Central Museum der Geneente Utrecht), 1951-1965 (Box 13, Reel 2125)
    - India (Baroda Museum and Picture Gallery), 1953 (Box 13, Reel 2125)
    - Israel (The Israel Museum), 1965 (Box 13, Reel 2125)
    - Italy (Box 13, Reel 2125)
      - Rome (Palazzo Barberini), 1951-1953 (Box 13, Reel 2125)
      - Urbino (Palazzo Ducale), 1951 (Box 13, Reel 2125)
    - Spain (Box 13, Reel 2125)
      - Cadiz (Museo Provinciad de Bellas Artes), 1953-1965 (Box 13, Reel 2125)
      - Madrid (Museo Arqueologico Nacional), 1959 (Box 13, Reel 2125)
    - Sweden (National Museum), 1952-1962 (Box 13, Reel 2125)
    - United States (Box 14, Reel 2125)
      - California (Los Angeles County Museum of Art; Fine Arts Gallery of San Diego), 1953-1967 (Box 14, Reel 2125)
      - Connecticut (Wadsworth Athenaeum; Yale University Art Gallery), 1946-1964 (Box 14, Reel 2125)
      - District of Columbia (Dumbarton Oaks, Harvard University; National Gallery of Art), 1946-1966 (Box 14, Reel 2125)
      - Florida (Ringling Museum), 1953-1963 (Box 14, Reel 2125)
      - Illinois (Art Institute of Chicago), 1951-1959 (Box 14, Reel 2125)
      - Indiana (Art Association of Indiana/John Herron Art Institute), 1944-1959 (Box 14, Reel 2125)
      - Kentucky (J. B. Speed Art Museum), 1951-1952 (Box 14, Reel 2125)
      - Maine (Museum of Art of Ogunquit), 1955 (Box 14, Reel 2125)
      - Maryland (Baltimore Museum of Art; Walters Art Gallery), 1958-1962 (Box 14, Reel 2125)
      - Massachusetts (Box 14, Reel 2125)
        - Boston (Isabella Stewart Gardner Museum; Museum of Fine Arts), 1943-1966 (Box 14, Reel 2125)
        - Cambridge (Fogg Art Museum), 1933-1966 (Box 14, Reel 2125)
        - Northampton (Smith College Museum of Art), 1955-1959 (Box 14, Reel 2125)
        - Williamstown (Sterling and Francine Clark Art Institute; Williams College, Lawrence Art Museum), 1951-1966 (Box 14, Reel 2125)
        - Worcester (Worcester Art Museum), 1938-1967 (Box 14, Reel 2125)
      - Michigan (Detroit Institute of Arts), 1943-1966 (Box 14, Reel 2125)
      - Missouri (William Rockhill Nelson Gallery of Art), 1949 (Box 14, Reel 2125)
      - Nebraska (Joslyn Art Museum), 1961 (Box 14, Reel 2125)
      - New Jersey (Newark Museum; Princeton University Art Museum), 1940-1957 (Box 14, Reel 2125)
      - New York (Box 14, Reel 2125)
        - Brooklyn Museum; Buffalo Fine Arts Academy/Albright Art Gallery; Cornell University, White Art Museum; Cooper Union Museum, 1951-1963 (Box 14, Reel 2125)
        - Frick Collection, 1937-1961 (Box 14, Reel 2125)
        - Jewish Museum, 1965 (Box 14, Reel 2125)
        - Metropolitan Museum of Art, 1944-1966, (2 folders) (Box 14, Reel 2125)
        - Museum of Modern Art, 1951-1962 (Box 14, Reel 2125)
        - Rochester Memorial Art Gallery, 1964 (Box 14, Reel 2125)
      - North Carolina (North Carolina Museum of Art), 1958-1963 (Box 14, Reel 2125)
      - Ohio (Box 14, Reel 2125)
        - Cincinnati Art Museum; Cleveland Museum of Art, 1948-1967 (Box 14, Reel 2125)
        - Columbus Gallery of Fine Arts; Dayton Art Institute; Oberlin College, Allen Memorial Art Museum; Toledo Museum of Art, 1938-1963 (Box 14, Reel 2125)
      - Oregon (Portland Museum of Art), 1955 (Box 14, Reel 2125)
      - Pennsylvania (Box 14, Reel 2125)
        - Alverthorpe Gallery, 1951-1966 (Box 14, Reel 2125)
        - Philadelphia Museum of Art, 1950-1967 (Box 14, Reel 2125)
      - Rhode Island (Rhode Island School of Design Museum of Art), 1959 (Box 14, Reel 2125)
      - Texas (Museum of Fine Arts of Houston), 1949-1955 (Box 14, Reel 2125)
      - Vermont (Bennington Historical Museum and Art Gallery), 1950 (Box 14, Reel 2125)
      - Virginia, Norfolk Museum of Arts and Sciences; Virginia Museum of Fine Arts, 1954-1965 (Box 14, Reel 2125)
  - Libraries, 1941-1967, 1.4:
    - Belgium (Bibliothèque Royale de Belgique), 1955-1965 (Box 14, Reel 2125)
    - Canada (Oratoire Saint-Joseph), 1962 (Box 14, Reel 2125)
    - England (Box 14, Reel 2125)
      - Canterbury (Lambeth Palace), 1951 (Box 14, Reel 2125)
      - London (Wellcome Historical Medical Library), 1957-1962 (Box 14, Reel 2125)
      - Oxford (Bodleian Library), 1951 (Box 14, Reel 2125)
    - France (Box 14, Reel 2125)
      - Paris (Bibliothèque de l'Arsenal; Bibliothèque Nationale), 1951-1964 (Box 14, Reel 2125)
      - Rouen (Bibliothèque de la Ville de Rouen), 1947-1954 (Box 14, Reel 2125)
    - Germany (Universitäts-bibliothek), 1953-1962 (Box 14, Reel 2125)
    - Holland/Netherlands (Koninklinjke Bibliotheek), 1948 (Box 14, Reel 2125)
    - Italy (Box 14, Reel 2125)
      - Florence (Biblioteca Nazionale), 1952 (Box 14, Reel 2125)
      - Milan (Biblioteca Ambrosiana), 1951 (Box 14, Reel 2125)
      - Rome (Biblioteca Apostlica Vaticana), 1945-1964 (Box 14, Reel 2125)
    - Switzerland, Geneva (Bibliothèque, Universitaire), 1951 (Box 14, Reel 2125)
    - United States (Box 14, Reel 2125)
      - California (Henry E. Huntington Library and Art Gallery), 1959 (Box 14, Reel 2125)
      - District of Columbia (Library of Congress), 1947-1964 (Box 14, Reel 2125)
      - Illinois (Newberry Library; University of Chicago Library), 1960-1961 (Box 14, Reel 2125)
      - Massachusetts (Box 14, Reel 2125)
        - Boston Athenaeum, 1958 (Box 14, Reel 2125)
        - Fogg Museum of Art Library, 1949-1962 (Box 14, Reel 2125)
        - Harvard University Library, 1949 (Box 14, Reel 2125)
      - New Jersey (Box 14, Reel 2125)
        - Institute for Advanced Study, 1952-1957 (Box 14, Reel 2125)
        - Princeton University, Firestone Library, 1954-1966 (Box 14, Reel 2125)
        - Princeton University, Marquand Library, 1951-1961 (Box 14, Reel 2125)
      - New York (Box 14, Reel 2125-2126)
        - Frick Art Reference Library; Jewish Theological Seminary Library, 1941-1962 (Box 14, Reel 2125-2126)
        - Pierpont Morgan Library, 1943-1966 (Box 14, Reel 2125-2126)
        - New York Public Library, 1953 (Box 14, Reel 2125-2126)
      - United States, Pennsylvania (Free Library of Philadelphia), 1960 (Box 14, Reel 2125-2126)
      - United States, Texas (Library of the University of Texas, Austin), 1958 (Box 14, Reel 2125-2126)
      - United States, Wisconsin (Ripon College Library), 1967 (Box 14, Reel 2125-2126)
  - Colleges, Universities, and Institutes, 1936-1968, and undated, 1.5:
    - A-Z, General (single letters, Albany, State University of New York - Wooster, College of), 1941-1968, (2 folders) (Box 14, Reel 2126)
      - Albany, State University of New York at (Box 14, Reel 2126)
      - Archaeological Institute of America (Box 14, Reel 2126)
      - University of Arkansas (Box 14, Reel 2126)
      - University of Auckland (Box 14, Reel 2126)
      - Bauerische Akademie der Wissenschaftsgeschichte (Box 14, Reel 2126)
      - Bennett College (Box 14, Reel 2126)
      - Boston College (Box 14, Reel 2126)
      - Boston University (Box 14, Reel 2126)
      - Bowling Green State University (Box 14, Reel 2126)
      - Brandeis University (Box 14, Reel 2126)
      - Université de Bruxelles (Box 14, Reel 2126)
      - Colgate University (Box 14, Reel 2126)
      - Dalhousie University (Box 14, Reel 2126)
      - Denison University (Box 14, Reel 2126)
      - Drew University (Box 14, Reel 2126)
      - Ellis Island for Higher Education, Inc. (Box 14, Reel 2126)
      - Emma Willard School (Box 14, Reel 2126)
      - Emory University (Box 14, Reel 2126)
      - Freiburg, Albert Ludwigs Universitat (Box 14, Reel 2126)
      - Frieburg, Die Kunstwissenschaftliche Gesellschaft (Box 14, Reel 2126)
      - University of Hawaii (Box 14, Reel 2126)
      - Indiana University (Box 14, Reel 2126)
      - Karel van Mander Kunsthistorische Instituut (Box 14, Reel 2126)
      - Louisiana State University (Box 14, Reel 2126)
      - University of Louisville (Box 14, Reel 2126)
      - Universität Marburg (Box 14, Reel 2126)
      - Massachusetts Institute of Technology (Box 14, Reel 2126)
      - University of Nebraska (Box 14, Reel 2126)
      - New School (Box 14, Reel 2126)
      - University of North Carolina (Box 14, Reel 2126)
      - University of North Dakota (Box 14, Reel 2126)
      - Nova Scotia Technical College (Box 14, Reel 2126)
      - Ohio Wesleyan University (Box 14, Reel 2126)
      - University of Oklahoma (Box 14, Reel 2126)
      - Universita di Pavia (Box 14, Reel 2126)
      - Philadelphia College of Art (Box 14, Reel 2126)
      - Pomona College (Box 14, Reel 2126)
      - Reed College (Box 14, Reel 2126)
      - University of Rhode Island (Box 14, Reel 2126)
      - Rockford College (Box 14, Reel 2126)
      - Rockefeller Institute (Box 14, Reel 2126)
      - Rollins College (Box 14, Reel 2126)
      - Royal Swedish Academy of Letters, History and Antiquities (Box 14, Reel 2126)
      - Saint Meinrad Seminary (Box 14, Reel 2126)
      - State University College on Long Island (Box 14, Reel 2126)
      - Temple University (Box 14, Reel 2126)
      - University of Texas (Box 14, Reel 2126)
      - University of Toronto (Box 14, Reel 2126)
      - Washington University (Box 14, Reel 2126)
      - Wayne State University (Box 14, Reel 2126)
      - Weil Institute (Box 14, Reel 2126)
      - Western Michigan University (Box 14, Reel 2126)
      - Western Reserve University (Box 14, Reel 2126)
      - Wilson College (Box 14, Reel 2126)
      - College of Wooster (Box 14, Reel 2126)
    - Académie Royal de Belgique - Bard College, 1950-1968 (Box 15, Reel 2127)
      - Academie Royal de Belgique (Box 15, Reel 2127)
      - American Academy in Rome (Box 15, Reel 2127)
      - Amherst College (Box 15, Reel 2127)
      - Bard College (Box 15, Reel 2127)
    - Bowdoin, College, 1953-1956 (Box 15, Reel 2127)
    - Brown University, 1946-1960 (Box 15, Reel 2127)
    - Bryn Mawr College, 1937-1964 (Box 15, Reel 2127)
    - University of Buffalo - University of California, Los Angeles, 1939-1967 (Box 15, Reel 2127)
      - University of Buffalo (Box 15, Reel 2127)
      - University of California, Berkeley (Box 15, Reel 2127)
      - University of California, Los Angeles (Box 15, Reel 2127)
    - Carleton College - Carnegie Institute of Technology, 1951-1964 (Box 15, Reel 2127)
      - Carleton College (Box 15, Reel 2127)
      - Carnegie Institute of Technology (Box 15, Reel 2127)
    - Center for the Study of Democratic Institutions, 1960-1961, undated (Box 15, Reel 2127)
    - University of Chicago - University of Colorado, 1944-1962 (Box 15, Reel 2127)
      - University of Chicago (Box 15, Reel 2127)
      - Colby College (Box 15, Reel 2127)
      - University of Colorado (Box 15, Reel 2127)
    - Columbia University, 1952-1965 (Box 15, Reel 2127)
    - Connecticut College - Courtauld Institute of Art, 1941-1967 (Box 15, Reel 2127)
      - Connecticut College (Box 15, Reel 2127)
      - Cooper Union (Box 15, Reel 2127)
      - Cornell University (Box 15, Reel 2127)
      - Courtauld Institute of Art (Box 15, Reel 2127)
    - Dartmouth College - University of Delaware, 1940-1959 (Box 15, Reel 2127)
      - Dartmouth College (Box 15, Reel 2127)
      - University of Delaware (Box 15, Reel 2127)
    - Duke University - Goucher College, 1948-1957 (Box 15, Reel 2127)
      - Duke University (Box 15, Reel 2127)
      - Florida State University (Box 15, Reel 2127)
      - Goucher College (Box 15, Reel 2127)
    - Harvard University, 1936-1966 (Box 15, Reel 2127)
    - Haverford College - Hobart and William Smith Colleges, 1954-1966 (Box 15, Reel 2127)
      - Haverford College (Box 15, Reel 2127)
      - Hobart and William Smith Colleges (Box 15, Reel 2127)
    - University of Houston - University of Illinois, 1942-1965 (Box 15, Reel 2127)
      - University of Houston (Box 15, Reel 2127)
      - University of Illinois (Box 15, Reel 2127)
    - Institute for Advanced Study, 1939-1966 (Box 15, Reel 2127)
    - Institute of International Education - Jewish Theological Seminary, 1939-1965 (Box 15, Reel 2127)
      - Institute of International Education (Box 15, Reel 2127)
      - State University of Iowa (Box 15, Reel 2127)
      - Jewish Theological Seminary (Box 15, Reel 2127)
    - Johns Hopkins University, 1946-1966 (Box 15, Reel 2127)
    - University of Kansas - Lowell Institute, 1948-1968 (Box 15, Reel 2127)
      - University of Kansas (Box 15, Reel 2127)
      - University of Kentucky (Box 15, Reel 2127)
      - Kenyon College (Box 15, Reel 2127)
      - University of London (Box 15, Reel 2127)
      - Lowell Institute (Box 15, Reel 2127)
    - Manhattanville College of the Sacred Heart - Middlebury College, 1946-1964 (Box 15, Reel 2127)
      - Manhattanville College of the Sacred Heart (Box 15, Reel 2127)
      - Michigan State College (Box 15, Reel 2127)
      - University of Michigan (Box 15, Reel 2127)
      - Middlebury College (Box 15, Reel 2127)
    - University of Minnesota - University of New Hampshire, 1949-1960 (Box 15, Reel 2127)
      - University of Minnesota (Box 15, Reel 2127)
      - Mount Holyoke College (Box 15, Reel 2127)
      - University of New Hampshire (Box 15, Reel 2127)
    - New York University, 1945-1966 (Box 15, Reel 2127)
    - New York University, Institute of Fine Arts, 1937-1967, (2 folders) (Box 15, Reel 2127)
    - Northwestern University - Oberlin College, 1937-1964 (Box 15, Reel 2127)
      - Northwestern University (Box 15, Reel 2127)
      - University of Notre Dame (Box 15, Reel 2127)
      - Oberlin College (Box 15, Reel 2127)
    - Ohio State University, 1952-1964 (Box 15, Reel 2127)
    - University of Oregon - Pennsylvania State University, 1954-1964 (Box 15, Reel 2127)
      - University of Oregon (Box 15, Reel 2127)
      - Oxford University (Box 15, Reel 2127)
      - Pennsylvania State University (Box 15, Reel 2127)
    - University of Pennsylvania, 1946-1960 (Box 15, Reel 2127)
    - University of Pittsburgh, 1959-1964 (Box 15, Reel 2127)
    - Princeton University (general), 1938-1966 (Box 15, Reel 2127)
    - Princeton University, Department of Art and Archaeology, 1940-1967 (Box 15, Reel 2127)
    - Richmond Area University Center, Inc. - University of Rochester, 1947-1954 (Box 15, Reel 2127)
      - Richmond Area University Center, Inc. (Box 15, Reel 2127)
      - University of Rochester (Box 15, Reel 2127)
    - Rutgers University, 1946-1964 (Box 15, Reel 2127)
    - St. John's College, Annapolis - Skidmore College, 1945-1963 (Box 15, Reel 2127)
      - St. John's College, Annapolis (Box 15, Reel 2127)
      - St. John's University, Minnesota (Box 15, Reel 2127)
      - Sarah Lawrence College (Box 15, Reel 2127)
      - Skidmore College (Box 15, Reel 2127)
    - Smith College, 1951-1965 (Box 15, Reel 2127)
    - University of Southern California - Uppsala University, 1952-1962 (Box 15, Reel 2127)
      - University of Southern California (Box 15, Reel 2127)
      - Swarthmore College (Box 15, Reel 2127)
      - Syracuse University (Box 15, Reel 2127)
      - Uppsala University (original letters filed under Paulsson, Gregor) (Box 15, Reel 2127)
    - Vassar College, 1938-1964 (Box 15, Reel 2127)
    - University of Virginia, 1941-1963 (Box 15, Reel 2127)
    - Warburg Institute, 1948-1966 (Box 15, Reel 2127)
    - University of Washington - Wellesley College, 1947-1968 (Box 15, Reel 2127)
      - University of Washington (Box 15, Reel 2127)
      - Wellesley College (Box 15, Reel 2127)
    - Wells College - Wheaton College, 1949-1957 (Box 16, Reel 2127)
      - Wells College (Box 16, Reel 2127)
      - Wesleyan University (Box 16, Reel 2127)
      - Wheaton College (Box 16, Reel 2127)
    - Williams College, circa 1954-1968 (Box 16, Reel 2127)
    - University of Wisconsin, 1954-1959 (Box 16, Reel 2127)
    - Yale University, 1955-1967 (Box 16, Reel 2127)
  - Organizations, Societies, and Congresses, 1937-1967, 1.6:
    - Académie Royale de Belgique - American Numismatic Society, 1956-1967 (Box 16, Reel 2127)
      - Académie Royale de Belgique (Box 16, Reel 2127)
      - American Academy of Arts and Letters (Box 16, Reel 2127)
      - American Academy of Arts and Sciences (Box 16, Reel 2127)
      - American Council of Learned Societies (Box 16, Reel 2127)
      - American Numismatic Society (Box 16, Reel 2127)
    - American Philosophical Society, 1955-1967 (Box 16, Reel 2127)
    - Amsterdam XVIIth International Congress??? - Brussels Ministère de l'Education???,1953-1967 (Box 16, Reel 2127)
      - Amsterdam XVIIth International Congress of the History of Art (Box 16, Reel 2127)
      - Belgian American Educational Foundation, Inc. (Box 16, Reel 2127)
      - Brussels Ministère de l'Education Nationale et de la Culture (Box 16, Reel 2127)
    - College Art Association, 1940-1961, (2 folders) (Box 16, Reel 2127)
    - College English Association??? - Medieval Academy of America, 1948-1964 (Box 16, Reel 2127)
      - College English Association, Committee for the Study of Mankind (Box 16, Reel 2127)
      - Colloquia Humanitas Conimbrigensia, Coimbra, Portugal (Box 16, Reel 2127)
      - Experimental Program in Teacher Education, Temple University (Box 16, Reel 2127)
      - Gottesman Foundation (copies; originals filed under Gottesman, D. S.) (Box 16, Reel 2127)
      - John Simon Guggenheim Memorial Foundation (Box 16, Reel 2127)
      - Hispanic Society of America (Box 16, Reel 2127)
      - Samuel H. Kress Foundation (Box 16, Reel 2127)
      - Medieval Academy of America (Box 16, Reel 2127)
    - Midwestern College Art Conference - United States National Student Association, 1937-1958 (Box 16, Reel 2127)
      - Midwestern College Art Conference (Box 16, Reel 2127)
      - National Council of Churches of Christ in the U.S.A., Department of Worship and the Arts (Box 16, Reel 2127)
      - New York Renaissance Club (Box 16, Reel 2127)
      - Phi Beta Kappa (Box 16, Reel 2127)
      - Renaissance Society of America (Box 16, Reel 2127)
      - Royal Society of Arts, London (Box 16, Reel 2127)
      - Society for the Protection of Science and Learning (Box 16, Reel 2127)
      - United States National Student Association (Box 16, Reel 2127)
    - John Hay Whitney Foundation - YMHA, New York, 1950-1960 (Box 16, Reel 2127)